Fine. Tell the truth.
Just give me a pound of flesh.
What do you want?
House wants to buy off of your skin. He sent me to get it.
And you agreed?
I had nothing to do with putting you in a coma or any of the subsequent tests.
Which brings us to now.
I read some of your articles.
There are a lot of them.
1967, Massachusetts Medical Journal.
You radiated babies. Just like that. No forms, no questions, nothing.
Who knows how many cancers you caused?
I don't know.
But I do know as we discovered techniques that prevent fatal kidney failures in hundreds of thousands of other kids.
You're not sorry.
I don't regret what I did.
Informed consent, patient rights, holdings, and so on.
Don't expect research.